# DEVON HACKLEY

# FULL-STACK DEVELOPER

### TECHNICAL SKILLS

JavaScript
HTML
CSS
Angular
Node
Firebase
Mongo
AWS
TDD
React

## PERSONAL SKILLS

Forward Thinking
Reliable and professional
Organized
Time management
Team player
Quick Study
Motivated

## CONTACT

P: 206-659-2953 E: devonhackley.dh@gmail.com GH: github.com/devonhackley

## **ABOUT**

Front-end oriented Developer who enjoys the challenges and triumphs of software development. I want to utilize my knowledge and previous experiences to continue my growth by building applications that not only reach users, and inspire them to grow, but also continue the growth and impact that technology has in our lives and future.

# **PROJECTS**

### HOMESECURE

link: homesecure.herokuapp.com code: github.com/rpcvjet/HomeSecure

• Two tier biometric home security application. Utilizes facial recognition and spoken password to grant entry.

### GOALTASTIC

code: github.com/devonhackley/goaltastic

• REST API, that allows users to track their progress on specific goals that they wish to accomplish.

## BARKRAWL

link: barkrawl.herokuapp.com/code: github.com/aer03280/Barkrawl

 Single Page web app, that utilizes the Yelp API and Google maps API to enable users to search nearby dog friendly bars in their area. Data is persisted through the use of a SQL database.

## **EDUCATION**

CERTIFICATE OF FULL-STACK JAVASCRIPT SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT

Code Fellows 2016-2017

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

TEACHING ASSISTANT

Code Fellows Mar. 2017 - Present

CUSTOMER SALES ASSOCIATE J.Crew Feb. 2016 - Jun 2016

AEROSPACE MEDICAL TECHNICIAN
U.S Air Force Dec. 2009 - Dec. 2013